<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">android50_anim_loading_screen</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_toggle">Toggle</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_activiti01_crossfading_views">Activiti01 Crossfading Views</string>
    <string name="my_very_long_string">
        You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and
        may provide additional or different license terms and conditions
        for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or
        for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,
        reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with
        the conditions stated in this License.

        5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,
        any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work
        by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of
        this License, without any additional terms or conditions.
        Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify
        the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed
        with Licensor regarding such Contributions.

        6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade
        names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,
        except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the
        origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.

        7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or
        agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each
        Contributor provides its Contributions) on an "AS IS" BASIS,
        WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or
        implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions
        of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A
        PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the
        appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any
        risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.

        8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,
        whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,
        unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly
        negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be
        liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,
        incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a
        result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the
        Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,
        work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all
        other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor
        has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

    </string>

</resources>

